Okay , ready ?
One , two ,
three .
Start again .
What are you doing here ?
This is the seniors ' toilet .
Where did you get that ?
Wanna see ?
Do you wanna try ?
Do you think it 'll fit me ?
No . But it 'll fit me .
Do you wanna try ?
Here , try !
Wait .
It 's hard to undo .
Nearly !
Let go , I 'll do it .
Here .
Don 't film me !
It fits .
I want to try next .
Open this door .
Open the door or I 'll call the disciplinary teacher .
Miss , the door 's stuck .
Maybe you can help push it open .
I 'll count to three .
One ,
two ,
three !
Zaffan !
What are you doing ?
What kind of person would think that 's fun ?
The toilets are communal areas ,
not your own private space .
Pull your sleeve back down !
Here is someone
who has no respect for her school ,
nor any consideration for her peers .
Who wants to join her ?
Come on !
Come up on the stage now !
Why can 't you seniors
set a good example for the juniors ?
Most of you will amount to nothing
if you carry on with this attitude .
Your final exams are only
a few months away .
And answer me this .
Why do only Chinese students get the top grades
every year ?
Where are the Malay students ?
Always causing trouble , and ending up here on stage .
Bye , Sir !
Give me a sticker .
Boring , they 're all just stars .
- I 'll stick it on your face ! - Not a blue one .
Stick it on Farah 's face .
Wait .
Stick it properly .
Zaf , your uniform is so pretty .
- Stick one there . - Here ?
My bag , you guys !
Did you stick it on my back ?
Nope .
- You did . - No , we didn 't .
It 's pretty ,
honestly .
Zaffan !
Hey , it 's cute .
No ! Don 't do that !
Kill it .
No .
Just let the poor thing go .
Okay ,
let 's play a game .
Whoever gets the wettest
will be cursed to eat live frogs
for ever and ever .
- Okay . - I don 't want to .
One , two , three !
It 's cold !
Serves you right !
You 're always showing off .
Now look who has to eat live frogs .
When do I show off ?
Why are you still wearing that ?
I could have got caught today .
I 've already said I 'm sorry .
Only sluts wear that sort .
Where did you even get it ?
Farah .
Okay .
Fine , I 'll take it off .
Peace be upon you .
And upon you .
Did you walk home like that ?
My uniform got wet .
Where ? Show me .
This is soaking wet !
If people get caught in the rain , do they strip off ?
Do they get naked like you ?
Maybe they should . Like this .
Stop it !
That hurts , Mum !
You stubborn thing !
You have no shame !
Mum !
Let everyone see you !
You bring shame on our family !
Mum !
What is it ?
You 're dirty now .
We 're safe .
It 's come out .
- Did you see that ? - It roared .
Idiot !
That 's dangerous .
Hey , I was watching that .
They 're gonna kill it .
Hey , Zaffan . Are you having a dump ?
Do you want us to wait for you ?
No , I 'm coming out .
That 's cool .
Let 's go .
Kiss !
Hurry , come on in .
Let 's think of names for our club .
Come in , then .
I don 't have to .
Why ?
Get in . We 're about to start .
Peace be upon you , class .
We promised that we 'd share everything .
You can 't keep secrets to yourself .
Farah !
Farah , give it back !
No . First you tell us everything .
No !
Are you okay ?
Farah , sorry .
It 's not like we don 't know .
Everyone 's talking about it .
The whole school 's saying you got your period .
But I get to skip prayers now , and you guys don 't .
Lucky .
It 's gross , though .
Why aren 't you eating ?
I 'm not hungry .
My mum said you can choke and die doing that .
Listen to this .
" In particular , one student had it worse .
" Ina was too careless in washing out her period pads .
" One night ,
she apparently went crazy and began laughing hysterically .
Not only that ,
she also threatened to run into the jungle alone at night . "
That 's bullshit !
- I 'm only reading what it says . - Let me see .
" Ina became more rebellious
to her parents and teachers .
" Eventually , she disappeared one evening ,
never to be seen again .
There are many witnesses
who claim to have seen her in the jungle . "
You should be careful .
I don 't want to be the first .
Does it hurt ?
I don 't know .
My sister always gets cramps .
And sometimes walks with her legs spread .
No ,
it 's the cleaning that 's a pain .
Then remembering to change your pad .
One time ,
my sister got blood on the sofa
when we were watching TV .
Her blood was dripping everywhere .
The smell was rotten ,
like the fish market .
My dad was so mad at her . It 's gross !
You know ,
you 'd better take care when cleaning yourself .
It says here that
if you don 't wash the blood off your pad properly ,
demons will lick that blood and follow you around .
I don 't want it to happen to me .
Look .
You can set it for two people .
See !
I want a phone too .
This phone is for all club members to use .
Let 's go .
Why ?
Let 's just go .
It 's nothing , probably just the wind .
Or maybeâ  ¦
it 's Ina .
Could you please not say her name ?
Why ?
You 're scared .
Yeah , you 're scared !
I 'm not !
Zaffan !
- We 'll sacrifice you to Ina . - Get off !
- Hold her legs , Mariam . - Don 't !
Ina 's going to eat you .
Don 't you dare do that to me again !
Slut !
What did you say ?
Mariam !
Zaffan !
The father _ to work .
How does the father _ to work ?
What is it ?
Sorry , Miss .
Can you pay attention during class ?
" Goes "
Correct .
The father goes to work .
Pay attention to the verb .
Understand ?
Alright , next .
The motherâ  ¦
Who can tell me ?
The mother _ at home .
The mother cooks at home .
Ok ?
It can wait , Zaffan .
I go , you go ,
he or she goes .
Got it ?
Ok , next one .
Please , Miss .
- I need to go to the toilet . - There 's only ten minutes left .
Student _ at home .
Who can tell me ?
Why didn 't you tell me earlier ?
This is really embarrassing .
You 're not a kid any more .
How can you still wet yourself ?
You should just go home .
She 's so gross .
How embarrassing , pissing herself !
Why 's she been so weird lately ?
I mean , who pisses themself ?
It was disgustingâ  ¦ and the smell !
I don 't think she even showers now .
The other day I thought I smelled something dead .
It was just her !
Maybe we should tell her .
What for ?
She has a nose .
She should be able to smell herself .
I just don 't want to sit next to her .
I need to breathe .
Of course . Nobody wants to sit next to her any more .
You 'd die from lack of oxygen !
Have you heard of that TikTok gwiyomi dance ?
- Yeah . Norzamrio , right ? - Yeah !
Guysâ  ¦
Over here , Farah .
Hey Mariam .
Can we walk home together today ?
I don 't think so .
Okay .
Butâ  ¦
I can wait until you guys finish .
Farah says we can 't .
There are more and more pests lately .
Rememberâ  ¦
when you used to help me clean my gun ?
Dad , I want to join the cadets .
Can we go and buy the uniform later today ?
Is it a school programme ?
Yeah . If you 're active in a co-curricular subject ,
you have a better chance of getting a scholarship for boarding school .
Let me talk to your mother about it .
Dadâ  ¦
where are you going ?
Can I come ?
Nice try , but you 're not skipping school .
One , two , three , fourâ  ¦ one group .
One , two , three , fourâ  ¦ next group .
One , two , three , fourâ  ¦ five . Five in that group .
Okay , start putting up your tents .
And remember ,
organisation and teamwork are important .
Let 's see which group finishes first .
Faster , faster !
Drink up .
If you don 't finish it ,
we 'll throw all your stuff into the river .
Let 's see
who can hold their pee
until tomorrow morning .
Don 't look up .
Something is watching you from the trees .
So don 't look up .
Farah , she 's looking up .
I said don 't look up !
I can 't sleep here .
When she went to pee ,
she said she saw someone looking down from that tree .
Why was she so stupid as to go alone ?
What if I need to pee later ?
Hold it in until morning .
Guys .
There were strange noises .
- Did anyone else hear them ? - What noises ?
Okay , enough !
Let 's all pray together .
Whoever 's awake get up now .
It 's all because of her .
Girls shouldn 't camp in the jungle when they 're on their period .
It 's disgusting .
They should check all the girls before they allow them on these trips .
I 'm not on my period any more .
That thing came last night
because it could smell her .
Cadets !
Gather round !
We have to pack up quickly .
The bus leaves in an hour .
Corporal Farah , a head count .
Twelve .
Twelve ?
Not thirteen ?
Has anyone seen Liyana ?
Who 's seen Liyana this morning ?
Juniors ? You were in the same tent as her .
Girls , please . Has anyone seen Liyana ?
Liyana !
I don 't want to spend another minute in this place .
Where 's your partner ?
Who cares ?
Liyana !
Cadets , make sure you stick with your partner !
Who 's there ?
Miss , I 've found her !
Come quick !
Are you okay ?
Why did you leave camp ?
You 're not supposed to wander around alone . It 's not safe .
The lady said that the seniors
wouldn 't be able to bully me up here .
What lady ?
Over here !
She 's up there .
Zaffan 's found her .
Liyana !
How did you get up there ?
Don 't try to climb down .
We 'll go for help .
I can go .
I can get the campsite manager .
You and you , go with her .
The youth cadets
successfully completed the recent weekend camp session .
I want to commend all of the cadets
for their achievements working as a team .
I 'd also like to give a special commendation
to our newest cadet member .
Not only did she pass all the required modules ,
she also showed natural leadership and bravery ,
which should set an example for others .
Please put your hands together for Nur Zaffan binti Azman .
Congratulations , Zaffan !
Students ,
you are only a few months away from your final exams .
Those who are at the top now
will likely succeed ,
while those who are at the bottomâ  ¦
I 'm not sure what 'll happen to them .
Once again I 'll read out the names of those at the top .
First , Chiew Xin Yee .
Second , Priya Nadesan .
Her name again !
Third , Nur Zaffan binti Azman .
Fourthâ  ¦
Farah binti Muhamad Zaid .
And fifth , Lim Khai Sim .
Congratulations to you all !
And good luck to our schoolâ  ¦
First you join the cadets ,
and now you want to be a prefect ?
I don 't want to be a prefect .
Why do you keep copying me ?
Can 't you leave us alone ?
Why would I want to copy you ?
I got third place . You got fourth .
I can 't do it .
Here , empty it out .
What 's wrong with you ?
Why are you wearing them ?
Why can 't I ?
Don 't be awkward .
We 're at home , take them off .
I don 't want to !
- Stop it , Mum ! - What 's got into you ?
Zaf ! Come here !
Go , then ! Don 't bother coming back !
I hate them all !
Come out .
She 's in there .
Go on .
Zaffan .
We want to check
you weren 't on your period at prayers today .
If you 're not hiding anything , you can just show us , right ?
Come out !
Don 't touch me !
Shut up !
Keep still !
I said keep still !
Is this for real ?
Guys , look at this .
Camera .
Farah , look at this .
Puteri , hold her legs down .
You 're a slut . You 'll be pregnant in no time .
You can be our human sacrifice .
Keep still !
You know what ? Your smell makes me sick .
Every time I see you I want to vomit .
Get away from me !
What 's happened to you ?
Miss , she won 't stop shaking . Help !
What happened here ?
Get her away from me !
She 's sick !
Take me home ! I need to clean my whole body .
Call the medical centre .
Sir , where are you taking her ?
Call the medical centre now !
Who has a phone ?
Doesn 't anyone have a phone ?
What 's going on ?
Get up !
Have you seen Farah ?
Students ,
as I was saying ,
I have someone very important here
to talk to you .
Let 's all listen carefully
to what he has to say to us today .
Please .
Peace be upon you .
I didn 't hear you answer my greeting ?
On the count of three ,
I want everyone to say :
" Good Morning , Dr Rahim . "
One , two , three !
Good morning , Dr Rahim .
I know it 's a pain , sitting there in the hot sun .
Look over there .
I think that even your teachers
are bored !
So trust me when I say
that I 'm not here to waste your time .
But you all need to understand
the reason I 'm here .
I 'm here to talk about something veryâ  ¦
serious .
Stand .
Good morning , Sir .
Good morning . Be seated .
I will take the register before we start class .
When I call your name , please raise your hand .
Alya .
Hani .
Apparently , Miss Azizah was affected too .
Who were the other girls there ?
They 've locked all the toilets and classrooms on the top floor .
Can the thing still be there ?
I don 't know .
It seems that none of them remember anything .
Eliza ?
Eliza is present .
Why are you late ?
Hurry up !
What 's your name ?
I 'm talking to you .
- What 's her name ? - Farah .
Farah .
Is Eliza present ? Oh , yes .
Zaffan .
Present .
Zaffan is present .
All right .
As you all know , I 'm replacing Miss Azizah today .
Farah .
Meet me at the disciplinary office after class .
Understand ?
Right , open your textbooks at chapter 6 .
Troops , line up !
Troops , straighten your lines .
Face forward .
At ease .
Stand easy .
Good morning , students .
Good morning , Miss .
I 'll now hand over to our troop leader , Izza ,
to do today 's marching practice .
Attention !
Go on , Izza .
Troops , left turn .
Check one , two .
Troops , from the left , forward march .
Left , right , leftâ  ¦
Stop !
Check one , two .
Troops , from the left , forward march .
Left , right , leftâ  ¦
Stop !
Check one , two .
Farah !
Move out of the way .
Tell it to go away !
Bring me my kit !
There 's a black shadow !
I saw it !
They 've all been affected by the presence of something dark .
Very dark .
Dr Rahim will try his best
to drive the evil presence far away .
You 're lucky .
The presence is still weak here .
The presence is still weak .
Once we find the sourceâ  ¦
we can banish it .
Come out !
I know you 're there .
You should leave !
Why ?
Don 't come near me !
Where are you ?
Come out !
I know you 're there .
I saw you when you were in the water .
Come out !
I don 't want to go back to school .
Neither do I.
Don 't film me .
I 'm not , I 'm just checking something .
You 're filming , I can see .
Okay .
Let 's live here for ever .
Yes , let 's !
We 'll build a treehouse .
I 'm serious .
I 'm serious too .
This place ,
right here .
No one can find us .
- Serious ? - Yeah .
- What are you playing with ? - A rock .
A rock ? And now you 're gonna throw it ?
I 'm not going back to school .
Stop this nonsense .
Let go !
Get out !
Don 't touch me !
You have to promise me
that she won 't get hurt .
- Peace be upon you . - And upon you .
You 're all welcome at my treatment centre .
If you need any assistance ,
any treatmentâ  ¦
my doors are always open .
Please feel free to contact me .
You can WhatsApp me ,
DM me on IG , or Facebook .
My Facebook page has plenty of testimonies .
Have a look . Share it , like it .
- Peace be upon you . - And upon you .
It 's strong here .
I feel a strong presence .
Mr Azman .
Madam .
Please sit closer .
That 's fine .
Those at the back can move in closer .
For you who are afraid ,
you can watch with your eyes closed .
No siblings ?
No .
What about her friends ?
I don 't want to .
I don 't want to sit next to her .
Look at your friend .
She 's suffering .
Don 't you want to help her ?
Don 't you want to see her better ?
Yes .
I do .
Hold her tight .
She 'll struggle and ask to be let go ,
she 'll howl , beg and cry for help .
But you have to remember that thisâ  ¦
this girl in front of you here is no longer your daughter .
We 'll start now .
You can use your phones .
You can film it on your phones .
Remember to tag Dr Rahim .
Okay , we 'll start .
If you don 't want to feel any more painâ  ¦
reveal yourself .
Come out .
It seems it doesn 't want to cooperate .
Give me my kit .
Ladies and gentlemen .
This product
never disappoints .
Hold her mouth open .
Open it .
Just a bit .
Keep patting . It wants to come out .
Let me go .
Where do you want to go ?
If I let you go , where will you go ?
If I set you free ,
you have to promise me you 'll never come back .
Can you ?
You 'll leave hereâ  ¦
banished .
How about that ?
Do you understand what I 'm saying ?
If I let you go ,
you have to promise you 'll never return .
Do you understand ?
It 's stubborn .
It 's really stubborn .
Let me go !
You see that ?
Okay .
Come out and reveal yourself . I want to see your face .
Come out now .
It hurts , right ?
Look .
Don 't touch me !
You feel that ?
Come out now .
What exactly is it that you want ?
What do you want ?
Come out .
Reveal yourself .
She doesn 't want anything !
Just let her go !
Be quiet !
- This looks fake . - Be quiet !
This guy 's a fraud .
Would someone like to take my place ?
Go right ahead .
Please .
What 's with this water nonsense ?
Leave !
Stop it ! Tell him to leave !
Come out and reveal yourself !
Come out now !
I 'll kill it !
Stop it !
Hold her down .
We have to beat her
until it reveals its true self .
Here , hit her .
Hold her down .
Hit her !
Go on , hit her !
Grab her .
Move away !
Don 't let that animal get away !
Catch it .
Can you grab your daughter ?
Go on .
Grab her !
Stop !
I would like
to wish all our seniors good luck
as they begin their final-year exams .
I hope you have all worked hard .
For those who are still not ready ,
l guess it 's too late now .
One more thing ,
because I 've had to remind you all too many timesâ  ¦
please pay close attention to the new curfew .
All students are to
be accompanied by a parent or guardian
when travelling to and from school .
I don 't want to see anyone
wandering off home alone .
Do you understand ?
I 'm going to find her .
She 's gone , Farah .
What are you wearing ?
Mariam .
Munah .
Let me just sit out here .
Maybe she 'll come back .
I want to wait for her .
Show me your uwu !
Where are you ?
I 've found you !
I know I 've found you !
I know you 're there !
Mariam , stop !
Wait for me !
Mariam !
Stop it !
It 's okay , Farah , I 'm fine .
It 's okay , Farah .
Okay , ready ?
One , two ,
three .